# **HUANG HUANG**

207.391.2772 | huang.h0709@gmail.com | Brooklyn, NY | www.linkedin.com/in/hhuang8

### PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

College Graduate trained in Software Engineering with 5 years of IT experience. A smart and witty professional with a strong passion and persistence for problem solving and finding better innovative ways of doing things. Excels in teambased environments enriched with time sensitive projects while keeping a keen eye to detail. Possesses excellent time management abilities complimented with a positive attitude and persistence to troubleshooting issues.

## **EDUCATION**

Per Scholas – Bronx, NY – Remote Training

Software Engineer Training

New York City College of Technology, CUNY, Brooklyn, NY

Bachelor of Technology, Computer Engineering Technology

Associate in Applied Science, Electromechanical Engineering Technology

Cumulative GPA: 3.65/4.00

Honors: Dean's List 2015-2019

## **TECHNICAL EXPERTISE**

HTML

CSS

JavaScript

Node.js

Express.js

React.js

MongoDB

SQL queries

Java

### **KEY TRANSFERABLE SKILLS:**

Inter-networking Technology
Software for Computer Control

Logic and Problem-Solving Comp Control Sys Design

C++ Programming I Robotics technology

#### PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES:

Python, HTML, SQL, C++, Assembly Language, Java, RobotC, Arduino IDE

## **PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE**

# Coalition for the Homeless | New York, NY | Network Administrator |

04/2022 - 5/2023

- Maintained and upgraded networks and servers, installed new hardware and applications, and monitored for updates.
- Administered third-party applications, ensured network security and connectivity, and manage user accounts.
- Managed users in the Active Directory (Windows 2019 Server) and Azure ADSync environment
- Administrated email access and activity on Microsoft 365
- Conducted Network Health check in Cisco Meraki and created Virtual Machine with vSphere in VMWare
- Modified group policy/security for inclusion/exclusions from Network files
- Oversaw DHCP scope address lease; reserve IP for devices and users and configured remote connection
- Worked with vendors such as Spectrum, Verizon, AT&T

## Union Settlement Association | New York, NY | IT Associate |

06/2021 - 4/2022

- Managed users in the Active Directory (Windows 2016 Server) environment
- Installed, troubleshot, and maintain IP network printers
- Administrated Google Workspace; managed user accounts and email groups
- Setup FortiClient VPN for remote access to organization network and shared drives
- Managed and troubleshot Cisco VOIP such as phone line and voicemail
- Configured and deployed Wireless Access points

### Brooklyn Navy Yard Development Corporation | Brooklyn, NY | IT Intern

09/2018 - 04/2019

- Provided technical support to over 250 faculty members through phone and email
- Installed JamF MDM software on company iPhone and iPads
- Administered Microsoft and Active Directory accounts
- Supervised Visitor Management system (ProxyClick)